

Whatsapp: +8801300771076

Skype: maidulit

Email: maidulimv@gmail.com

Github: https://github.com/Maidulweb

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/maidul-

islam-65645080/

# **SKILLS**

#### **FRONTEND**

- · HTML5
- · CSS3
  - · TAILWIND CSS
  - BOOTSTRAP 5
- JAVASCRIPT
  - · VUE JS
  - · REACT JS
  - NEXT JS
  - . JQUERY

#### **BACKEND**

- PHP
  - . LARAVEL

#### **DATABASE**

· MYSQL

## **VERSION CONTROL**

- GIT
- GITHUB
- BITBUCKET

#### **OTHERS**

- WEBPACK
- NPM
- OAUTH

# **MAIDUL ISLAM**

Web Developer

## **ABOUT ME**

Web Development professional with more than 2.9 years of experience in efficient and large-scale web-based systems development. I am proficient Frontend development in Vue JS, React JS, Next JS and moderate. Backend skills with an interest in Laravel framework. I love to write clean code and follow best practices.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

**Q** Jan, 2021 – July, 2024

Aholi ICT Ltd. (Mirpur DOHS)

# Web Developer

- Developed a web application for company
- Frontend using HTML5, CSS3 and JS( jQuery )
- Bootstrap css
- · Backend using PHP

Work: https://aholiict.com/

Mar, 2020 - Jan, 2021

Mastul Foundation (West Dhanmondi, Dhaka)

# Web Developer

- Developed a web application for company
- Frontend using HTML5, CSS3 and JS( jQuery )
- Backend using Laravel 8

**\( \rightarrow\)** Feb, 2019 - Mar, 2020

Mates Group (Nikunjo-2, Khilkhet, Dhaka)

## Web Developer

- Developed a website for company
- Frontend using HTML5, CSS3 and JS( jQuery)
- Backend using Laravel 7

# WORK:

http://matesworkforce.com.au/ http://globalconnex.com.au/

http://asc.net.au/

http://matesglobal.com/

## OTHERS WORK :

https://karentpay.com/

https://idealsc.co.uk/

https://bazaarbangladesh.com/

https://app.biyerjuti.com/

https://growmoreca.com/

https://hdllfreelance.com/

## **EDUCATION**

B.Sc (Hons) in Information Technology

University of Information Technology & Science, Dhaka